{"items": [{"question": "anything to view specially striking kind of.", "answer": "spectacle", "options": ["spectator", "spectacle", "spectacles", "spectacular"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Optical instrument consisting of a frame that holds a pair of lenses for correcting defective vision", "answer": "spectacles", "options": ["spectacular", "specious", "spectacles", "spectator"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Sensational in appearance or thrilling in effect", "answer": "spectacular", "options": ["spectacular", "spectator", "introspective", "specious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a person who looks on or watches", "answer": "spectator", "options": ["spectator", "specious", "retrospect", "introspective"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "having an appearance of truth or reason but false", "answer": "specious", "options": ["circumspect", "retrospect", "specious", "introspective"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "act or process of looking into oneself", "answer": "introspective", "options": ["circumspect", "introspective", "retrospect", "inspect"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "a survey of past time, events", "answer": "retrospect", "options": ["retrospect", "inspect", "circumspect", "prospect"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "watchful and discreet", "answer": "circumspect", "options": ["conspicuous", "prospect", "inspect", "circumspect"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "to view closely and critically", "answer": "inspect", "options": ["inspect", "perspicacious", "conspicuous", "prospect"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The possibility of future success", "answer": "prospect", "options": ["conspicuous", "perspicacious", "perspicuous", "prospect"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "easily seen or noticed", "answer": "conspicuous", "options": ["perspicacity", "conspicuous", "perspicuous", "perspicacious"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Acutely insightful and wise", "answer": "perspicacious", "options": ["perspicuous", "perspicuity", "perspicacity", "perspicacious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "clearly expressed or presented", "answer": "perspicuous", "options": ["acumen", "perspicuity", "perspicuous", "perspicacity"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "keenness of mental perception and understanding", "answer": "perspicacity", "options": ["acumen", "acute", "perspicacity", "perspicuity"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "clearness or lucidity as of an statement", "answer": "perspicuity", "options": ["acute", "acupuncture", "acumen", "perspicuity"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "keen insight", "answer": "acumen", "options": ["acupuncture", "acute", "punctual", "acumen"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "sharp or severe in effect", "answer": "acute", "options": ["punctual", "acute", "pungent", "acupuncture"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Treatment of pain or disease by inserting the tips of needles at specific points on the skin", "answer": "acupuncture", "options": ["spectacle", "punctual", "pungent", "acupuncture"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "strictly observant of an appointment or regular time", "answer": "punctual", "options": ["spectacle", "pungent", "spectacles", "punctual"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "sharply affecting the organs of taste or smell", "answer": "pungent", "options": ["pungent", "spectacle", "spectacles", "spectacular"], "answer_index": 1}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 35.txt", "total": 20}